"以法之名" 前情提要...
Previously on damages...
你和Patty联系上了吗?
Did you get any word from patty?
我已经告诉她 她得回来
I've told her that she's
got to come back here.
她不想回来
She doesn't want to come back.
你认为 Patty要杀了你以自保?
You think patty tried to
kill you to protect herself?
我努力要了结这案子
I am trying to settle this case.
更努力点
Try harder.
她要和我离婚
She's divorcing me.
也许我会告诉他关于你和
Gregory Malina的事
Maybe I'll tell him about
you and gregory malina.
给我5分钟时间 Ray
Give me five minutes,ray.
我认为撞车行凶逃逸
都是George Moore一手策划
I think george moore engineered
this whole hit- and-run.
我觉得是他泄漏了阿灵顿事件
逼迫你和解
I think he leaked arlington
to get you to settle.
George Moore做了一场秀
假装调查Frobisher
George moore made a big show
of going after frobisher.
你不信他真要那么做?
But you didn't believe he was?
我跟你说这些 可能会被灭口
I could get killed for what I told you.
如果你和Arthur Frobisher有牵连
我们会查出来
If there's a connection between you
and arthur frobisher,we will find it.
我和George Moore谈过了
I spoke with george moore.
你怎么这么蠢?
How could you be so stupid?
别回来了
Don't bother coming back.
谢谢你的建议...
Thanks for the advice...
但我想我不再需要这个了
but I guess I won't be
needing this anymore.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我告诉她我受够了
I told her I was sick of her bullshit.
你干什么了?
You what?
Ellen 你当助理律师 第一年工作
Ellen,you're a first-year associate.
Patty像我这么大时
会忍受像她那样的老板吗?
When patty was my age,do you think she
would have tolerated a boss like her?
不会
No.
那我为什么要忍?
Then why should I?
是因为案子吗?
Was this about the case?
部分是
Sort of.
我自己发现了些证据...
I uncovered some evidence on my own...
但Patty更感兴趣的是要我做
她安排的事 而不是我发现的证据
But patty was more interested in
putting me in my place than what I found.
我明白了
I see,mm-hmm.
她说一切都是为了案子 但不是的
She says it's all about
the case,but it's not.
一切都是她自己 及她的勾心斗角
It's about her and her mind games.
对
Yes.
我希望客户能赢得官司 但...
I want the clients to
win their case,but...
我不想成为Patty的出气筒
I'm not going to be
patty's punching bag.
你会卷土重来的
Oh,you'll bounce back.
所以我来找你 Nye先生
Which is why I'm here,mr.Nye.
我要一份工作
I need a job.
官司是永远打不完的 Ellen
The law will always be here,ellen.
你婚礼将近了 是吗?
But,um,your wedding
is coming up,isn't it?
对
Yes.
我早前工作时也犯过类似错误
You know,I made similar
mistakes early in my career.
都没度蜜月
Never took a honeymoon.
生命中美好时刻 不要错过
Don't let your life pass you by.
我知道
********
8天后
8 DAYS LATER
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
时间轴: 咔肉肉
翻译: elise aaron
校对: sade
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉
以法之名
第一季 第11集
Damages
Season01 Episode11
亲爱的 这简直是个噩梦
Babe,this is a nightmare.
什么事?
What is?
安排座位
The seating arrangement.
比律师考试还复杂
It's more complicated than the bar exam.
能让你表哥Jake坐在Heather旁边吗?
Can I sit your cousin
jake next to heather?
干吗总想给Heather找对象呢?
Why are you always trying
to pimp heather out,huh?
我只是觉得 他俩都...
I just thought,you know,they both...
都喜欢徒步旅行...
they both love hiking...
都喜欢嗑药
and narcotics.
他们有话题
they have lots to talk about.
Nye那边谈得如何?
How'd it go with nye?
他不愿意让我工作
He wouldn't give me a job.
他让我放个大假
He told me to take a vacation.
我爱死这家伙了
I love this man.
好吧 咱们晚点见
All right,I will see you later.
- 好吗?
- 好的
- Okay?
- Okay.
你好 David
Hello,david.
Patty
Patty.
我能进来吗?
May I come in?
你晚点给我电话?
Do you want to call me later?
好 我会的
Yeah. I will.
我一直在想 你何时出现
I was wondering when you would show up.
你搜集的文件让我惊叹
You impressed me with this.
我从来都没打算取悦你
I wasn't trying to.
搜集信息 利用信息而已
Just take the information and use it.
这资料很有吸引力
但对我们的案子有何帮助?
It's all very intriguing,but
how does it help our case?
George Moore曾负责证交会
对Frobisher公司的调查
George moore was heading up the sec
investigation into frobisher's company,
但据一位前任证交会调查员...
but according to a
former sec investigator...
Laura Watkins 据她说
Laura watkins.
我见过她
I met with her.
她相信Moore只是做秀
假装要扳倒Frobisher
She believed that moore was making a big
show of wanting to take down frobisher,
但却在背后暗地破坏调查
but behind the scenes he was
torpedoing the investigation.
剩下所有这些资料...
And all the
rest of this--
酒店入住记录 租车凭条 飞行记录...
the hotel records,the rental
car receipts,a flight manifest...
都显示Frobisher抛售股份前那个周末
All show that george moore
was in jacksonville,florida
George Moore在
佛罗里达州的杰克逊维尔
the weekend before
frobisher sold his stock.
Moore开车到棕榈海滩
向Frobisher告密
Moore drove down to palm
beach to tip off frobisher.
有意思的推理
It's a nice theory.
没证据证明
No proof.
那也要加以利用
Use it anyway.
给Moore施压
Put pressure on moore.
要干吗?
To do what?
逼Frobisher和解
Get frobisher to settle.
我之前不理解
为什么Moore要向我们泄密
I could never understand
why moore leaked arlington,
现在 全说通了
but now it makes perfect sense.
他一定害怕开庭后 一切真相大白
He must be afraid of what
would come out in a trial.
Moore希望案子快点结束
如果他发现你知道他的底细...
Moore wants the whole case to go away,and
if he knows that you're closing in on him...
会提供更多内情
供我们对付Frobisher
He'll give us more dirt we
can use against frobisher.
所以...
So...
我们得回头找Moore
we need to go back to moore.
我也这么认为
I think so.
我公司里 他只肯跟你一个人谈
And you're the only lawyer
in my firm he'll talk to.
这公寓不错
It's a nice apartment.
难道不是吗?
Isn't it?
回去找Moore吧
Go back to moore.
还有...
And...
当然 你能回来上班
of course you can have your job back.
我不想回去
I don't want it.
但我会和Moore谈谈
But I'll talk to moore.
我希望你能赢这场官司
I want you to win this case.
我们的上庭时间...
同志们 还有六周
Our court date--
six weeks,folks.
Tom要确认案子进展要点
如果他要你们做什么 就去办
Tom's running point,so if he
needs you to do something,do it.
提交证物 证人准备
Exhibits,witness prep.
这是最后期限
It is deadline time.
Felicia 专家名单有吗?
Felicia,do you have the expert list?
明天给你
You'll get it tomorrow.
就这样
That's it.
别让我失望
Make your mothers proud.
- Ellen今早去哪了?
- 不知道
- Where was ellen this morning?
- I don't know.
也许她不舒服
Maybe she wasn't feeling well.
Tom 办公室一半的人都看到
她几天前她大怒离开
Tom,half the office saw
her storm out the other day.
Patty解雇她了吗?
Did patty fire her?
把心思放在案子上
Just focus on the case.
所有人都在谈论这个
Everyone's talking about it.
- 该怎么跟他们说?
- 随你们便
- What are we supposed to tell them?
- Whatever you want.
告诉他们Ellen死了
Tell them ellen's dead.
把该死的专家名单给我就好
Just get me the goddamn expert list.
我希望她被解雇了
I hope she was fired.
我从不喜欢她
I never liked her.
Ray?
你好
Hey.
你怎么来这儿了?
What are you doing here?
我想你可能需要午餐
I thought you could use some lunch.
都有啥?
what do we got here?
一块不错的鱼排 芦笋
还有些黑莓馅饼
A nice filet,some asparagus,and
some blackberry cobbler.
亲爱的 太丰盛了
sweetie,this is stupendous.
我今早开完会
I finished my meetings this morning,
才感到有多想你
and i just realized
how much I missed you.
我知道 对不起
I know,I know,I'm sorry.
这案子占了我全部的生活
This case has just taken over my life.
所有案子都这样 Ray 但这个...
They all do,ray,but this one...
这件案子不同
this one's different.
我担心你
I worry about you.
你这些天很沉默
You're so quiet these days.
什么?
what?
你之前从没抱怨过我这些
You never accused me of that before.
是真的
Well,it's true.
只要这案子一结束
我又会变回标准的老话匣子
Soon as the case is over,I'll be
a regular ol' chatterbox again.
那不错
Well,that'll be nice.
我们可以花几天时间
去塔科玛看你姐姐
We'll take a few days,go
see your sister in tacoma.
真去了我才信
I'll believe that when I see it.
我保证
I promise.
坐 坐 吃饭
Sit,sit,eat.
闻起来不错
Oh,that smells good.
亲爱的 再见
********
2002年5月
MAY 2002
还来点酒?
More wine?
干吗不呢?
Why not?
我们马上打烊了 所以...
We're going to be closing soon,so...
看起来我是你最后一位顾客
Looks like I'm your last customer.
我只是忘了时间
I suppose I just lost track of the time.
你总来这里忙工作 你做什么的?
You're always coming in here
with work. What do you do?
我是律师
I'm an attorney.
我还不知道你叫什么
You know,I don't believe
I've ever caught your name.
Greg
Greg.
我叫Ray
Ray.
大停电?
A blackout?
你大概还在幼儿园呢
You were probably still in kindergarten.
是1977年 我来这里第一周
This was 1977,the very
first week I arrived.
- 真是开张大"吉"
- 见鬼
An auspicious debut. Shit.
猜我什么时候来这里的
Guess when I got here.
什么时候?
When?
去年9月
Last september.
- 不是嘛
- 对
You don't say. Yeah.
是去年9月之前 还是之后?
Before or after?
9月前
Just before.
差点改主意 但我想...
It almost made my change my
mind,but then I thought...
如果我现在离开...
if I leave now...
他们就赢了 对
They win. Right.
尽管 我可能早该离开
I probably should have left,though.
为什么这么说?
Why's that?
我不知道 我...
I don't know,I...
我只是...
I just can'T...
坚持不下去了 明白?
get going,you know?
我住在个鸟地方 挣的刚够交房租
I live in a shithole,and i
barely make enough to pay my rent.
你当初为什么决定来这里?
Why did you decide to move
here in the first place?
想尝试尝试
I'll try anything once,I guess.
不好意思
Oh,I'm sorry.
是我太太
That's my wife.
你结婚了?
You're married?
从没见过她 你没带她来过
Never seen her; you never bring her in.
我是来工作的 要保持头脑清醒
Oh,I come in here to work,clear my head.
你喜欢做律师吗?
You like being an attorney?
我喜欢律师和客户间的关系
I like the relationship
between attorney and client.
是一种亲密 一种信任
There's an intimacy there,a trust.
有人将他自己交到你手上
Someone puts himself in your hands.
你喜欢这样
And you like that.
我喜欢
I do.
你在这儿干吗?
What the hell are you doing here?
楼下的夫妇说天花板漏水
Oh,uh,a couple downstairs
said the ceiling was dripping.
只是...
Just,um...
检查一下是否有渗漏
checking for a leak.
那你弄灯干吗?
And the lamp?
发现灯泡坏了
Noticed a bulb was out.
Ellen知道你在这里吗?
Does ellen know that you're here?
不知道
No.
Patty Hewes让我特别关照你们
Patty hewes told me to
extra special care of you.
下次 请先给我打电话
Next time,you call me.
别再这么干
Don't ever do this again.
6天后
6 DAYS LATER
你有57条新留言
You have 57 new messages.
Patty 我是Tom
Patty,it's tom.
我是Tom
it's tom.
我在罗马 我很担心你...
I'm in rome now.I'm worried about you...
我是Tom...
it's tom...
妈 我在Henry家 一切都好...
Yeah,mom,I'm up at
henry'S.Everything's fine...
我不知道怎么跟你说
I don't know how to tell you this.
我刚接到Hollis Nye的电话
I just got a call from hollis nye.
不知道什么原因 Ellen进监狱了
Somehow,ellen's in jail.
我不知道怎么跟你说
I don't know how to tell you this.
我刚接到Hollis Nye的电话
I just got a call from hollis nye.
不知道什么原因 Ellen进监狱了
Somehow,ellen's in jail.
她因为涉嫌谋杀David被捕
She was arrested for killing david.
锯齿草坪如何?
How was sawgrass?
什么?
I'm sorry?
你一路17杆打上草坪
还是最后落水?
Did you hit the green on
17 or end up in the drink?
取决于你指的是什么
Depends on when you're talking about.
2002年6月
June,2002.
Frobisher抛售股票前一周
你在佛罗里达州的杰克逊维尔
You were in jacksonville,florida the
weekend before frobisher dumped his stock.
对
Ah,yes.
我打中了草坪
I hit the green.
那是啊
I'm sure you did.
然后你开车4小时到棕榈海滩
向Frobisher告密
Then you drove four hours to palm
beach and tipped off frobisher that
说证交会打算公开一份报告
揭发他公司的财务问题
the sec was about to release a
report damning his company's finances.
Frobisher给了你丰厚回报?
Frobisher give you a nice kickback?
我当时正努力起诉Arthur Frobisher
I was trying to prosecute
arthur frobisher.
Laura Watkins可不是这么说的
Not according to laura watkins.
我不知道你怎么想...
Look,I don't know what you think...
我想你希望案子结束
I think you want this case to be over,
我想我们能互相帮忙
and i think that we can help each other.
告诉我关于Frobisher的秘密
Give us something on frobisher.
如果我不呢?
And if I don't?
Patty Hewes会盯上你
Then patty hewes
starts looking into you.
你的财务状况 投资 银行帐户...
Your finances,your
investments,your bank accounts--
任何你藏起来的 她都会查出来
anything you have hidden,she'll find it.
我告诉过你
我没法交出Frobisher
I told you,I can't give you frobisher.
但是我能交给你另外一个人
But I can give you somebody.
谁?
Who?
明晚同样时间 这里见
Same time,tomorrow night,meet me here.
我会给你带份礼
I'll bring you a present.
天哪...
Jesus...
你吓到我了
you scared me.
- 你以为就你自己的时候 特可爱
- 是吗?
You're so cute when you
think you're alone. Yeah?
不过别太激动
是Marge阿姨和Fran叔叔送的
Don't get too excited,though. It's
from aunt marge and uncle fran.
土地神?
A garden gnome?
我们住公寓
We live in an apartment.
天哪 你家人真有品味
Thank god your family has some taste.
Patty说什么了?
What did patty have to say?
她要我回去工作
She offered me my job back.
你怎么说?
What did you say?
我拒绝了
I said no.
很好
Good.
我不喜欢她出现在我们生活里
I don't like having her in our lives.
我也不喜欢
Neither do I.
- 要早餐吗?
- 当然
- You want breakfast?
- Sure
不
Aw,no.
谁?
Who is it?
Lila Dimeo
Lila dimeo.
别接
Don't answer it.
但这是她这周打来的第三次了
But this is the third time
she's called this week.
我们得想个办法
这些骚扰电话让我火大
Well,we need do something.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
你跟Toomey法官那边谈的如何?
How did it go with judge toomey?
Patty 你什么时候宣布解雇Ellen?
Patty,when are you going
to announce ellen's firing?
我在办公室躲躲闪闪
回避同事的问题...
I'm-I'm-I'm running around the
office,avoiding people's questions...
然后?
And?
我现在是合伙人
我希望你把我当合伙人对待
And I'm a partner now,and I
need you to treat me like one.
如果你对Ellen有什么安排
我该知道
If you have plans for
ellen,i need to know them.
没安排
There are no plans.
那你该告诉同事
Then you should tell
the associates that.
Ellen联系了一个关键的线人
却没告知我们 她被解雇了
Ellen approached a key informant
without our knowledge,and she was fired.
大家该知道这些
People should know that.
去通告大家吧
Go announce it.
谢谢
Thank you.
Tom?
And,tom?
你说得对 你是合伙人
我该开始像对合伙人那样对你
You're right,you're a partner,i
should start treating you like one.
见鬼 Gregory 你就一个任务
Goddamn it,gregory,you had one task.
一个任务 你还搞砸了
One task,and you screwed it up.
我怎么知道那家伙提前出现了?
How was I supposed to know the
guy was gonna show up early?
你一开始就不该去那间公寓
You shouldn't have been in
the condo in the first place.
你该租好了 留下钥匙 去度假
You were supposed to rent it,leave
the key,and take a goddamn vacation.
对不起 Ray
I'm sorry,ray.
不过告诉你吧 那女孩什么也没看见
But I'm telling you,the
girl didn't see anything.
现在最重要的是你啥也别说
The important thing now
is for you to say nothing.
把这件事彻头彻尾忘记 明白？
You just forget any of this
ever happened,understand?
知道了
Yes,I understand.
我很抱歉 刚才我对你大吼大叫
Look,I'm sorry for
raising my voice at you...
是我的错
It's my fault.
我..我搞砸了
I-I screwed up.
我派你过去的
I'm the one who sent you down there.
听着
Listen.
为了派你去那边 而给你的报酬
That gift I gave you,for
going down there...
股票
The stock.
帮你自己个忙
Do yourself a favor.
明天把它卖了
Sell it tomorrow.
给我杯双份苏格兰威士忌
Give me a double scotch.
你相信吗?
Do you believe this?
我现在住在酒店
I'm staying in a hotel room.
我不能回到那座房子
I can't be in that house anymore.
你得给我找个最好的离婚律师
You better get me the best goddamn
divorce attorney in this city.
当然
Of course.
一场官司 一场官司的解决
One battle at a time.
谢谢  那足够了
Thank you,that's enough.
Art...
我们猜对了
we were right.
什么猜对了
About what?
George Moore
George moore.
他出卖你的
He sold you out.
阿灵顿那件事....
Arlington...
还有Gregory Malina...
gregory malina...
都是他干的 他出卖了你
it's all him.
你呆会要和Moore见面吗？
So you're meeting with moore again?
是的
Yeah.
他不愿意供出Frobisher
但是他愿意供出其他人
He won't give up frobisher,but
he's going to give us someone else.
你已经让他绝望了
You've got him desperate.
他想在案子波及他之前就结束
He's trying to make the case go
away before it closes in on him.
如果Moore向Frobisher告密
那也是犯法的
If moore tipped off
frobisher,that's a crime.
你干吗不以这项罪名告他?
Why shouldn't we just
go after him for that?
因为要以我们的委托人为优先
Because our clients come first.
刑事控告优先考虑
Criminal charges would take precedence.
我们的案件会被推迟上3年
Our case could get pushed
another three years.
我们早晚会告他的 Ellen
We'll get there,ellen...
一步一步来
once step at a time.
给你
here.
这是干吗?
What's this?
这够你用几周的
It should hold you over for a few weeks.
我不是为了钱
I'm not doing this for money.
我知道你不是 拿去吧
I know you're not,but take it.
不要犯傻了 Ellen
Don't be foolish,ellen.
总要吃饭吧
Everyone needs to eat.
- 妈妈
- 什么事
Mom? Yeah.
嘿..
Oh,hey.
不好意思打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
Michael 这是Ellen Parsons
Michael,this is ellen parsons.
你好
Hi.
很高兴见到你 Michael
Nice to meet you,michael.
真好
Yeah,cool.
你今天晚上用车吗？
Are you using the car tonight?
我 Henry还有Julius
今天晚上要去Foxwoods
Me,henry and julius are
going to head to foxwoods.
去赌场?
To the casino?
你进不去
You can't get in.
妈... 用假身份证啊?
Mom... fake ids?
祝你们有个愉快的晚上
You guys have a nice night.
她还挺辣的
She's kind of hot.
你究竟去哪了 我等了将近...
Where the hell have you
been?I've been waiting for over...
你确定你没事吧
Are you sure you're all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
给你
Here.
真遗憾你经历了这些
I'm sorry you went through that.
我恨这些人
I hate these people.
这些照片将Ray Fiske和
Gregory Malina联系在一起
Photos link ray fiske to gregory malina,
还有文件可以证明
Fiske内幕交易的罪行
and the documents prove that
fiske's guilty of insider trading.
这对你应该有用
you should be able to use that.
这是勒索 Ellen
It's blackmail,ellen.
去做你该做的吧
Just do what needs to be done.
Frobisher先生提出用5亿和解
但Patty Hewes拒绝了
So mr.Frobisher offered $500 million to
settle,and patty hewes turned it down.
如此高价 按理说这个案子就该结束了
at that price,this case should be over.
她对自已力量估计太高了
She's overplaying her hand.
她坚信Arthur在采证庭里
Gone and convinced herself that
的爆发足以让她在陪审团
面前一搏
arthur's outburst in that deposition room will
be worth more to a jury than it actually is.
我祖父很喜欢你 Ray
My grandfather adored you,ray.
我还听说 人们以为你是他儿子
I'm told people thought
you were his son.
他是一个好人
还是个非常好的导师
He was a fine man,an even better mentor.
他肯定会为你的功绩而骄傲
Marshall
He'd be tickled pink to see what
you've made of yourself,marshall.
我们都很尊敬你 Ray
We all have the utmost
respect here for you,ray.
真的
We truly do.
我有话直说了
So I... I won't mince words.
高级合伙人对你处理这件案子
的能力失去了信心
The senior partners have lost confidence in
your ability to effectively try this case.
你一定在开玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.
你知道
And as you know,
Frobisher先生案子的结果
对这公司的未来有很大的影响
mr.Frobisher's case bears enormous consequence
to the future well-being of this firm.
合伙人们都想你现在别插手这个案件
The partners want me to
shadow you from here on out.
开庭后 所有策略方面的决定
你都要先征求我的意见
You'll consult me on any and all
tactical decisions as we move to trial.
Arthur Frobisher是一个很顽固的人
Look,arthur frobisher is a stubborn man.
顽固而且善变
Stubborn and complicated.
也就让这个案子的难度
超越了普通方法可以应付...
There are complexities to the case
that are beyond the normal scope of...
Ray...
Look,ray...
Marshall 抱歉 没有冒犯的意思
Marshall,I'm sorry,no offense,
但是我得跟Amos谈谈才可以
but I'm going to have to
talk this over with amos.
已经成定局了
It's been decided.
我会监督你的每一步
所以....
I'll be looking over your shoulder
every step of the way,so...
你要把你手上所有的资料上交
you'll turn over everything you've got,
在周末前让我接手
get me up to speed by
the end of the week.
你嘴里是什么 宝贝
What do you have there,girl?
让我看看
Let me see.
来...
Come on.
来... 张开嘴
Come on,girl,open up.
你可真喜欢狗啊
Don't you just love dogs?
是的
Yeah.
它们跟人很像
They're like people.
只不过没人那么麻烦
Only without the bullshit.
玩去  去
Go play,girl,go.
你委托人的代表有重新考虑
我们开出的价钱了吗?
Client reps rethink the offer?
这是什么
What's this?
这是我们的反击筹码
It's our counter.
出钱让Gregory Malina去弗洛丽达
的有钱老板
The wealthy patron who paid gregory
malina's way down to florida,
就是你吧 Ray
I'm guessing it was you,ray.
你从哪弄到的?
Where'd you get these?
有什么所谓吗?
Does it matter?
只是一些照片 Patty
They're just pictures,patty.
代表不了什么
They don't mean... anything.
看那文件
Read the document.
你把股票转让给了Gregory Malina
You transferred stock to gregory malina,
然后利用你从委托人那里
得到的消息让他抛售
then told him to sell using
information you got from your client.
你才不理会你的私人生活 Ray
I don't give a shit about
your private life,ray.
- 但是我不能放着这样的信息不用
- Patty...
- But I can't sit on this kind of information.
除非你和我能达成协议
Unless you and I come
to some arrangement.
Frobisher没可能开出更高的和解价钱
There is no way frobisher is going
to offer you a better settlement.
我也不想和解
I don't want one.
这件案子将在法庭上审判
This case is going to
be tried in a courtroom.
我不会故意打输官司
I am not tanking my own case at trial.
考虑一下吧 Ray
Think about it,ray.
花时间仔细想想
Take your time.
没什么要想的
I don't have to think about it.
Frobisher是我的当事人
Frobisher's my client.
还是我朋友
And my friend.
如果Gregory Malina还活着
我们也不用进行这段对话
We wouldn't be having this conversation
if gregory malina were still alive.
Ray 你是浸会教徒吧
You're a baptist,right,ray?
忏悔吧
Repent.
谢谢
Thank you.
Phillips呆会想和你谈谈
Mr.Phillips wants to
sit down with you later.
我会过去的
I'll be here.
我们刚收到第二份结婚礼物
I think we just got
our second wedding gift.
- 真的
- 是啊
Really? Yeah.
可能是Barbara阿姨送的
It's probably from aunt barbara.
她告诉我 上个星期她从网上定了东西
She told me she ordered
something online last week.
哦  等一下
Okay,hang on,mom.
你知道
- You know,
- Hang on.
网上订购不像人们说的那么简单
ordering gifts on the internet
is not as easy as people say.
我想在登记页面想找你的名字
I tried to find your
name on the registry page,
但光在纽约市的就有
六个叫Ellen Parsons的
but there were six ellen
parsons in new york alone.
不管怎样 这就意味着你得开始
寄感谢卡了
Anyway,you know this means you're going
to have to start sending thank you notes.
天啊
Oh,my god.
怎么了?
What?
谁会寄这玩艺?
Who would send this?
什么东西?
What is it?
亲爱的 给你寄了什么?
Honey,what is it?
我想你 David
爱你的 Lila
I miss you David Love Lila
嘿 Ellen
Hey,ellen?
怎么了?
What's going on?
你还有Lila Dimeo的电话号码吗
Yeah,do you still have
lila dimeo's phone number?
有吧
yeah,I think.
你好 我是Lila
Hey,there,it's lila.
对不起 我现在不能听电话
但你知道该在什么时候做什么
Sorry,I'm not around,but i bet ya
know what to do and when to do it.
是Ellen Parsons
This is ellen parsons.
离我未婚夫远点
Stay away from my fianc?
要不然我发誓我会对付你
你这个疯婆
or i swear to god I will come
after you,you crazy bitch.
两天后
2 DAYS LATER
我们结束了 Ellen
We're done,ellen.
喂?
hello?
Lila 别说了 别说了
Li... stop,stop it.
停  听我说
Just stop. Listen to me.
该死的! 不!
Damn it,will
you just-- no!
Lila  你不要再打电话给我了
Lila,you need to stop calling me!
刚才...
That was,uh...
真的很愉快 Ray
that was great,ray.
谢谢晚餐
Thanks for dinner.
- 要庆祝你找到新工作
- 恩
- Had to celebrate your new job.
- Yeah.
2002年七月
JULY 2002
穿着西装上班肯定会觉得别扭
It's gonna feel strange
going to work in a suit.
你穿很好看
Looks good on you.
谢谢
Thanks.
Gregory...
怎么了?
What is it?
我们不能再见面
We can't be in contact anymore.
为什么
Why not?
看情形 政府要起诉我的委托人
Looks like the government
is charging my client.
我什么也不知道
I... I don't know anything.
我们知道就够了
You know enough.
我们不能被看到在一起
We can't be seen together.
好的
Okay.
Gregory 我会想你
I'm gonna miss you,gregory.
Ray 我也会想你
I'll miss you too,ray.
Gregory...
什么
What?
到底想说什么?
What is it?
- 不  Ray
- Gregory 求你了
- No,ray...
- Gregory,please.
求你了
Please...
不要  Ray 请你别这样
No,ray,come on. That'S...
我不是那种人
that's not who I am.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
Ray
Ray.
求你了
Please.
天啊 Ray
Jesus,ray!
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 Ray
I'm sorry,ray.
对不起...我...
I'm sorry. I...
什么事 Ray?
What is it,ray?
George Moore死了
George moore is dead.
听说了
I heard.
我收到一封信
I got a letter...
- Gregory Malina写的
- 什么时候写的?
- from gregory malina.
- When?
一切都结束了 Art
It's over,art.
什么结束了?
What is?
都结束了
It's over.
Ray 什么结束了?
Ray,what's over?
Ray 你究竟在说什么...
Ray,what the hell are you talking ab...
嘿
Hey.
Mallory
Mallory.
现在几点了
what time is it?
吃饭了没
Did you eat?
冰箱里有烤鲑鱼
There's some grilled
salmon in the fridge.
早上要做的第一件事
First thing in the morning...
就是离开
we have to leave.
- 去哪 我姐家
- 不是
- To go where,my sister's?
- No...
我们要离开这个国家
we have to get out of the country.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我明天再和你解释
I'll explain everything tomorrow.
现在你要做的是 收拾东西
Right now I need you to pack our things.
Ray 你得告诉我这到底是....
Ray,you have to tell me what...
Mal...
你要相信我
you have to trust me.
你能做到吗?
Will you do that?
是的
Yes...
当然
yes,of course.
好的
Okay.
我有一些事情要处理
I have a few things I
have to take care of.
收到我的留言了?
You got my message?
恩
I did.
那...
Yeah,so...
我一直在反复考虑
I've been mulling things over.
我想跟你坐下来谈谈
看能不能了结这件事
I'd like to sit down with
you,see how we can work this out.
真高兴听你这么说
I'm glad to hear it,ray.
我们明天一早就可以见面
We can get together first
thing in the morning.
能不能早点?
I'd prefer sooner.
我不想再让事情拖下去 你能明白吗?
I don't want this hanging
over me,you understand?
当然
Of course.
今晚迟些你要做什么?
What are you doing later tonight?
你让我去哪儿我就去哪儿
I can be anywhere you want me to be.
这是我四个月以来
第一次一路醒着看完的电影
Yeah,it was the first movie I saw in,like,
four months where I actually stayed awake.
- 那好
- 是啊
- OK
-Yeah
再过一个小时 我就回家
*****
宝贝 我爱你 再见
Okay,babe.I love you
我也爱你
Love
嘿 Ray
Hey there,ray.
你好 Patty
Hello,patty.
要喝点什么吗
You want a drink?
不用了
Thanks,no.
坐
Well,sit.
你最近可还好啊?
how you holding up?
好多了
I've been better.
我有没有告诉你我做律师的原因
Ray?
Did I ever tell you why
I became a lawyer,ray?
你没有和我说过
No,you never told me.
我以为我能改变世界
I thought I could change the world.
傻吧
Silly,huh?
我只是想每天都能带领带
I just liked getting
to wear a tie every day.
你和我就好像硬币的两面
You and I are two
sides of the same coin.
怎么说呢？
How's that?
我们喜欢较量
We love the game.
痴迷案件 追求赢大案子
Another case,a bigger win.
这比任何事情都让我们上瘾
It's an addiction like any other.
你在勒索我 Patty
You're blackmailing me,patty.
是的
Yes.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你我心知肚明
Long as we're clear.
Frobisher是有罪的
Frobisher is guilty,ray.
帮我伸张正义
Help me set things right.
你是我朋友
You're a friend.
我们能激出对方的真本领
We bring out the best in each other.
这个案子之后 我们还能交手
不知多少个回合
After this,we have a
hundred more rounds to go.
我觉得不大可能
I don't see how that's possible.
我不是想摧毁你
I am not looking to destroy you.
我们做律师的 最后都能挺过来
We attorneys survive.
而委托人却来的来 走的走
It's the clients that come and go.
我不能在法庭上
I can't go into a courtroom...
故意打输自己的案子
and deliberately lose my case.
Ray  我知道那很痛苦
I know it will be painful,ray.
但是从现在开始的六个月或一年后
一切都风平浪静
But six months,a year from
now,it'll all blow over,
你过来跟我一起工作
and you'll come work with me.
Patty...
我认真的
I'm serious.
你真的会请我?
You would do that?
雇用我所交锋过的最厉害的
辩护律师?
Hire the finest goddamn litigator
I've ever come up against?
我当然会那么做 Ray
Yes,ray.
当然
Absolutely.
这里的职位非你莫属
There's a place for you here.
这对我们来说是双赢
It's win-win,for both of us.
好吧 Patty
Okay,patty.
很好 Ray
Good,ray.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
你知道...
You know...
我一直想和你一起工作 Patty
I always wanted to work with you,patty.
但我不再想跟你一起工作了
Not anymore.
-------------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
-------------------------------
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
时间轴: 咔肉肉
翻译: elise aaron
校对: sade
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉